Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. This
is salted caramel almond.
>> What does that mean?
>> It just means like that's fire.
>> That's good.
>> If my biggest critic approves, then it's
got to be good. So, let me show you how
to make it. We're starting off with a
vanilla bean base. So, high protein
milk, sweetener, salt, zantham gum, and
some vanilla bean paste. So, we're going
to blend that all together with an
immersion blender, and then throw it in
the freezer for at least 16 hours. Then,
we're going to take it out, run it in
hot water for about a minute, and then
throw it in your creamy almond light ice
cream setting. Once it comes out, you
have two options. You can put the
chocolate and almonds on top, which
creates a chocolate shell and keeps the
almonds a little bit bigger, or you can
mix in the chocolate and almonds and
create fudge flakes throughout the pie,
which will also break up the almonds a
bit, give you more uniform bites. And
either way, we're topping it with some
salted caramel sauce. And it's going to
be absolutely delicious no matter which
you choose.